Guide to the Lloyd R. Simons Director of Extension papers, 1932-1935.
Simons, Lloyd R., Director of Extension papers, 1932-1935.
- Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- E, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Epsilon Sigma Phi, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- F, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Federal Land Bank Springfield, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- G, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Senior Statistician - R. Gillett, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- G. L. F. Exchange, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Grange - (National), 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Grange - (New York State), 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- H, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Hotels, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- I, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- J, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- K, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- L, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- M, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Applications and Registrations, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Letters Referred to Other Departments, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Requests for Bulletins, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Requests for Lists, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- N, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- New York State Bankers Association, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- New York State Conservation Department, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets - Peter Ten Eyck, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- New York State Education Department, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- New York State Federation of Home Bureaus, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- New York State Seed Improvement Association, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- New York State Vegetable Growers Association, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- O-R, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- S, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- T-Z, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Office of Cooperative Extension, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Business Manager Extension Service - M. Thayer, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- H. Hochbaum, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Director of Extension - C. Warburton, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Assistant Director - C. Smith, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 42-45)
- Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- History of Cooperative Extension, 1924-1968 (Box 7, Folder 49-55)
- Nassau County Farm Bureau News, 1915-1916 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- New York State Grange, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Seneca County Farm Bureau Miscellany, 1928-1939 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Course S-3 Term Paper "The Family" (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Miscellany (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Photographs - Including 20th Anniversary Party (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Volume - The Association of Teachers of Agriculture, New York, 1911-1941 (Box 7)
- Volume - Extension Organization and Policy by L. Simons (Box 7)
- Volume - Extension Organization and Leadership Development by L. Simons (Box 7)
- Scrapbooks (Box 8)